One Pace Premium
Keep the project alive: ko-fi.com/not6ip
Let's go! Shining! Running! Forever
Keep pushing forward!
The bonds that joins us will never break
and its light will shine on the end of our dreams.
Wake up! Wake up! Wake up! Wake up heart beat!
We are the one! Go ahead!
Freedom is our only compass we need. -We are best friends-
We'll be the ones to carve out our own route.
We spend all our days moving full speed ahead, -Go east, Go west-
each day brings something new and we leave nothing unfinished.
I'm too excited to wait for morning to come. (I can't wait)
And so we might as well just grab the sun,
And forcefully drag it into the sky! Go!
That's right, we're Shining! Running! Forever!
Weave the fragments of our dreams together!
When they become one, that will be our treasure!
Let's go Shining! Running! Forever
Keep pushing forward!
The bond that joins us will never break
and its light will shine on the end of our dreams.
Wake up! Wake up! Wake up! Wake up heart beat!
We are the one! Go ahead!
Darkness will consume you, Straw Hat!
I won't lose! I'll find One Piece. I'm gonna be the Pirate King!
Every trial we overcome brings a chance for thrills. (I can't stay)
Tomorrow and each day after will be heated, intense.
A chain of excitements!
That's right! Shining! Running! Forever!
Trust your curiosity, follow your heart
and head for your goal, that's what adventure is all about!
Let's go shining! Running! Forever!
Spread open the chart of your dreams!
There's power hidden in the bond between us,
it'll help us grasp the end of our dreams.
Never! Never! Never! Never stop it!
We are the one! Go ahead!
Corrida Colosseum!
The Great Tournament
Who is that guy?
Was that a devil fruit ability?
Probably, but what type of ability was it?
I'm very sorry for the trouble.
You can send the request for compensation to this address.
Uh, I see...
What?!
Sir, are you...?!
Excuse me.
You're really strong, old guy! Who are you?
It would seem...
that it'd be better for the both of us if I didn't tell you.
Hey! Why don't you watch where you're going?!
I-I'm very sorry. Are you hurt?
Better for the both of us?
Is he like, some really infamous guy?
Whoever he is, he's definitely trouble.
My bag's gone!
And my watch!
Where'd my wallet go?!
Damn it! My jacket's been stolen!
Even though it's midday,
they still managed to sneak in through the dust!
Did the old guy pickpocket everyone, or something?
One of them is missing!
What do you mean?
One of my swords is gone!
Shuusui was right here!
What?! The treasure of the Wano Country?!
It seems everyone's been had.
The fairies stole them.
What's that supposed to mean?!
Is it some sort of criminal organization?
Fairies are fairies.
You just have to laugh and accept what they do.
The fairies cannot be seen, but they have been the guardians of Dressrosa for generations.
We must turn a blind eye to whatever they do.
Guess there's nothing for it.
You gotta be kidding me!
Indeed!
That is a national treasure of the Wano Country!
What?! It's my sword!
It does not belong to you!
Sooner or later I will fight you for the blade and return it to its rightful home!
Suits me fine! I'll just take you down!
Your greed was your downfall, fairies!
You're not getting away from me!
Hey Zoro, Where are you going!?
Hold it!
We don't have time to let you wander off on your own!
Looks like fun.
Not so fast, Luffy.
Have you found the culprit?!
I will not let you run off
with one of the Wano Country's treasures!
Let go of me! I want to go too!
I've got a great idea.
Idea?
I've come to realize that, in this group,
I have to take the lead or nothing will get done.
Just leave it to me, the bro-meister.
You're one of Doflamingo's men, aren't you?
Is that supposed to scare us?
We asked you a question, mister. Better spill the beans.
I-I already told you!
Yeah, I remember chasing the samurai, but I have no idea how he was captured or where he is now.
And I've never heard of this Smile-thing before.
Not even the letter S in Smile?
Nothing at all!
And that goes for this factory of yours too!
What are you talking about?!
Well, this ain't good.
Even his own men don't know, huh?
Then tell us where we can find someone who gives you orders!
This guy might just be too low in their ranks.
I have no idea where anybody is today.
Everyone's too busy.
Even I've been called to the colosseum.
Look.
People from all over the country
are heading to the colosseum today.
The Corrida Colosseum.
If you wanna find the higher-ups, go there.
Today's a special event.
The Family's commanders are probably gonna be there.
I dunno the details,
but the young master's prepared a spectacular prize.
I couldn't believe it when I found out.
It's something anyone would want.
You don't mean...
that ultra-delicious meat
that Mingo was talking about?!
He only said that it was something you'd want.
Ow!
Dressrosa's Corrida Colosseum
It's him! The Thunder Soldier!
Ladies, gentlemen and toys...
That hurts!
We wanna see too!
Let us in!
Children are not allowed to watch people fight to the death!
Go home!
The event today...
will be a truly special occasion!
For this day, the King has granted us...
a priceless gem!
Two years ago, at the Great War at Marineford...
a man lost his life.
He was second commander of the legendary Whitebeard Pirates, and the son of the Pirate King.
Ace!
They say his fists of flame could pierce warships...
or burn cities to the ground
and turn them into a living hell!
This formidable power has returned to the world.
Reborn in the form of a new Devil Fruit!
R-Reborn?
Seriously?!
Behold!
This forbidden fruit
will be given to the victor of today's battle!
One of the Logia Devil Fruits,
the strongest of the three varieties!
The Flame Fruit!
Is that true?
The young master
would never lie about something like this!
Ace's...
Flame Fruit?
Today our colosseum will be host to...
great men from all parts of the New World
who have been summoned by our King.
However! This gem will not be handed over easily.
If anyone thinks they can steal it,
I'd like to see them try!
It is being guarded by people far more powerful
than our usual combatants.
Namely...
members of the esteemed Donquixote Family!
Senor Pink!
Dellinger!
Lao G!
Machvise!
Vise!
And last but not least, the hero of our colosseum...
Mr. Diamante!
Diamante-sama!
Diamante!
Let's get this thing started!
Let's see some blood!
What... is Ace's Flame Fruit doing here?
Each devil fruit is unique
and no two have the same power.
But when a devil fruit user dies,
the fruit that holds that power will reappear again somewhere in the world.
And whoever eats the new fruit
will become the next holder of its power.
After Fire Fist Ace died,
the Flame Fruit reappeared somewhere unnoticed.
Until the young master managed to find it!
He's giving away a Logia devil fruit as a prize for his business.
The young master is much more generous than he needs to be.
I'm sure my life would be changed if I could gain that amazing power.
Like hell I'd let you eat it!
Oh yeah, Ace was your...
I want that Flame Fruit!
Oh, I know! Why don't you eat it, Franky?
I'd rather not become an anchor.
I've already eaten the Rubber Fruit,
so I can't eat another one...
but I don't want some random stranger to run off with Ace's power!
So it's like a memento for you?
Thinking of what Doflamingo said,
this is probably a trap.
All I'll say is...
Don't let this chance slip away!
You'd just end up regretting it.
Besides, we've got business at the colosseum anyway.
So let's go.
You fools.
If wanting it was all it took,
nobody would lose their lives there.
You underestimate the danger of the colosseum.
Mysterious Fairy Pursuit
Fairy, my ass! He's just some thief!
I keep telling you to wait!
Surely you can lose a sword. Or two!
Like hell I can, you damned idiot!
Dammit! Where did he go?
What's that?
Did you find the fairy?
Dancer
Violet
Such sweetness!
Such passion!
No one in the world can match your dancing!
What?
Sh-
She's so beautiful!
Have you forgotten
that women in this country stab men to death?
You're just gonna wind up dead.
I'd gladly let her stab me!
Shit! I lost sight of him!
That Moss-Head got himself lost!
Right, this is an excellent opportunity.
Let's just leave him here.
He's nothing but trouble anyway.
I did everything I could.
Looks like this place is filled with couples.
I'm really jealous.
I wonder if this place would make
Nami-san and Robin-chan hopelessly fall for me?
Hello, you there!
You're the one who was looking at me earlier, right?
Please...
hold me in your arms!
Whaaat?!
Where did she run off to?
She must have snuck out the back door into Lovers' Avenue. She can't be far!
Don't let her get out of the city!
Yes sir!
Thank you. It looks like they're gone.
Umm...
you can let go now.
Oh, you are very welcome.
I'm so sorry! Did you hit your head?
No, the only thing that has hit me is the impact of our meeting.
But there's so much blood!
No... it's nothing.
Poor you.
It's no use! I cannot resist this passion!
No, you mustn't look at me like that!
I have forsaken love.
Every man I've gotten involved with-
I know!
They were all in paradise!
You were being chased, right? Who were those people?
If there's anything I can do to help, just tell me!
That was the police.
I... stabbed a man to death...
because our love had turned sour.
What?!
You mean it's true?! Women in this country really are passionate enough to kill?!
Okay!
You're okay with that?!
What's wrong?
No, you can't just forgive a demonic woman like me!
Or I might...
fall in love with you.
My name is Violet.
Would you be so kind
as to escort me to the next town?
And once there...
will you kill a man for me?
Corrida Colosseum
The colosseum is enormous!
Just listen to those cheers!
Suddenly, I wanna participate too.
They're really getting fired up.
You've caused so much trouble!
Just give up already!
Criminal toy soldier!
No good! You can't hit me!
Jet Walk!
Look, my dear slugs!
I have entered the colosseum!
One-legged soldier
Alternate Name: The Mad Thunder Soldier
You know the law, don't you?
Cops and marines
are forbidden to enter the colosseum!
Even if you see criminals within the colosseum, you have no authority here!
The only law that applies in here
is the law of the Donquixote Family!
Pull those triggers, and you will be the criminals!
Now get out of my sight!
Dammit.
Oh, pardon me old man!
Shall I carry your luggage for you?
What's this? He sure got real polite all of a sudden.
What a funny soldier!
You find me funny?
How about this? How about this?
Could you step aside, pops?
Oh, am I in your way? How terribly rude of me!
You're blushing like crazy!
You're really serious, huh?
N-Not at all!
Making people smile is a toy's duty!
As if there could ever be such a thing as a serious toy!
He's taking it personally!
The open sign-up for today's battle
is about to close.
Not that any commoners
would want to participate, anyway.
They're too scared.
Hey, Luffy. Looks like that's your entrance over there.
Oh, I see.
Alright, I'm participating! Sign me up!
I'll fight!
Huh? Does that old man want to enter?
Is he nuts?
Does he have any idea what he's doing?!
Hey Luffy, listen. Promise me just one thing.
You can go all out if you want but don't ever let them know who you are.
Okay!
Sign your name.
Luf...
You idiot!
Fighter Number 556 - Lucy
This is the dressing room for the competitors.
You're free until we call you.
Wow! It's so exciting!
The Flame Fruit is mine!
No, it's mine, idiot!
Hey, who's the little guy?
I see.
Can we use any weapons we like?
Hey, who is he?
Oh, he's the last participant to sign up.
What's this shrimp doing here?
This is the worst kind of joke!
Spartan
Corrida Colosseum Gladiator (51 Time Winner of the Monthly Tournament)
Hey, fake-bearded brat! This is a fighting arena!
Don't, Spartan!
It's no fun seeing a weakling get pummeled!
The spectators only get excited when the strong go head-to-head!
This is not a place for you! Go home!
Go home now!
Nice to meet ya'!
Translation & initial timing, Yibis Fansubs, Tsuki
Timing, Galaxy 9000, , Time-checking, Sewil
Quality-checking, Sewil, Galaxy 9000
Soundtracking, Halee
Video editing, Sewil
Raw provider, Crunchyroll